[
    {
        "question_number": 101,
        "question": "Which of the following can be an external data source for a ServiceNow application?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Microsoft Excel File",
            "B": "Data provided by a public web service using SOAP or REST",
            "C": "CSV file",
            "D": "All of the above"
        },
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 102,
        "question": "Which one of the following is true for the Application Picker and Application Scope?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Global is a reserved application which does not appear in the Application Picker",
            "B": "Selecting an application from the Application Picker does not set the Application Scope",
            "C": "Selecting an application from the Application Picker sets the Application Scope",
            "D": "Selecting Global in the Application Picker sets the Application Scope to Incident"
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 103,
        "question": "Which of the following is an available feature in Studio? (Choose two.)",
        "options": {
            "A": "Push to update set",
            "B": "Merge branches",
            "C": "Search code",
            "D": "Push to external source control"
        },
        "answer": "CD"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 104,
        "question": "The Task table is an example of which of the following? (Choose two.)",
        "options": {
            "A": "Parent class",
            "B": "Legacy class",
            "C": "Child class",
            "D": "Base class"
        },
        "answer": "AD"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 105,
        "question": "Which of the following is true about deleting fields from a table?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Table records are deleted when a field is deleted",
            "B": "User-defined non-inherited fields can be deleted",
            "C": "Any field on a table can be deleted",
            "D": "Inherited fields can be deleted"
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 106,
        "question": "Why would you build a custom app? (Choose two.)",
        "options": {
            "A": "To avoid using a code repository like GitHub or GitLab",
            "B": "To replace ServiceNow base tables",
            "C": "To fulfill a specific use case on internal processes",
            "D": "To create a custom integration for a 3rd party system"
        },
        "answer": "CD"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 107,
        "question": "What are three ServiceNow table creation methods? (Choose three.)",
        "options": {
            "A": "Using legacy Workflows",
            "B": "Upload and turn a spreadsheet into a custom table",
            "C": "Using Flow Designer",
            "D": "Use the Now Experience Table Creator",
            "E": "Extend a table",
            "F": "Create a custom table"
        },
        "answer": "BEF"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 108,
        "question": "When selecting a data type for a field that will be displayed on a form, which of the following statements is NOT correct?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Use the String data type tor a free-form text field",
            "B": "Use the Phone Number data type to automate phone number data validation",
            "C": "Use the Choice data type to limit options in a field",
            "D": "Use the Date data type to enter the date and time of day"
        },
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 109,
        "question": "Which one of the following is NOT part of the Form Designer?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Page header",
            "B": "Schema map",
            "C": "Field navigator",
            "D": "Form layout"
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 110,
        "question": "Which class is NOT part of the Client side scoped APIs?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Glide Dialog Window",
            "B": "GlideAjax",
            "C": "GlideRecord",
            "D": "GlideForm"
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 111,
        "question": "When designing and creating a form what do you create to organize fields on a form?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Buttons",
            "B": "Tabs",
            "C": "Sections",
            "D": "Related lists"
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 112,
        "question": "Which one of the following is a good practice for adding instructions to a form?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Related links to wiki pages",
            "B": "A Context Menu UI Action",
            "C": "Annotations",
            "D": "A populated read-only field"
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 113,
        "question": "Which of the following GlideRecord methods run a query against a database table? (Choose three.)",
        "options": {
            "A": "_get()",
            "B": "runQuery()",
            "C": "query()",
            "D": "_query()",
            "E": "get()"
        },
        "answer": "CDE"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 114,
        "question": "What is the GlideForm Client-side scripting object?",
        "options": {
            "A": "sn.form",
            "B": "g_form",
            "C": "gs.form",
            "D": "gs_form"
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 115,
        "question": "In a Business Rule, which one of the following returns the sys_id of the currently logged in user?",
        "options": {
            "A": "g_form.getUserID()",
            "B": "gs.getUserSysID()",
            "C": "gs.getUserID()",
            "D": "g_form.getUserSysID()"
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 116,
        "question": "In which order are the elements of an Access Control evaluated?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Conditions, Roles, Script",
            "B": "Conditions, Script, Roles",
            "C": "Roles, Conditions, Script",
            "D": "Script, Conditions, Roles"
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 117,
        "question": "Assume a table called table exists and contains 3 fields: field1, field2, field3. Examining specific Access Controls (table.None: admin/itil, table.*: admin, table.field3: itil), which field or fields can a user with the itil role read?",
        "options": {
            "A": "All fields except field3",
            "B": "field1, field2, and field3",
            "C": "field1 and field3",
            "D": "field3 only"
        },
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 118,
        "question": "Assume a table called table exists and contains 3 fields: field1, field2, field3. Examining specific Access Controls (table.None: admin/itil, table.field3: admin), which field or fields can a user with the itil role read?",
        "options": {
            "A": "field3 only",
            "B": "filed1 and field3",
            "C": "All fields",
            "D": "All fields except field3"
        },
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 119,
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a caller access field option?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Caller Tracking",
            "B": "Caller Restriction",
            "C": "None",
            "D": "Caller Permission"
        },
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 120,
        "question": "Which method is used to retrieve Application Property values in a script?",
        "options": {
            "A": "gs.getProperty()",
            "B": "g_form.getAppProperty()",
            "C": "g_form.getProperty()",
            "D": "gs.getAppProperty()"
        },
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 121,
        "question": "What Module Link type is used to access an Application Properties page?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Single Record",
            "B": "HTML (from Arguments)",
            "C": "URL (from Arguments)",
            "D": "Script (from Arguments)"
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 122,
        "question": "Identify the way(s) an application can respond to an Event generated by the gs.eventQueue() method.",
        "statement_options": {
            "a": "Script Action",
            "b": "Scheduled Script Execution (Scheduled Job)",
            "c": "UI Policy",
            "d": "Email Notification"
        },
        "selection_options": {
            "A": "b and c",
            "B": "c",
            "C": "a and d",
            "D": "a and c"
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 123,
        "question": "When troubleshooting and debugging notifications, where do you navigate to see if an email was sent in response to an event?",
        "options": {
            "A": "System Logs > Events",
            "B": "System Logs > Emails",
            "C": "System Logs > Push Notifications",
            "D": "System Logs > ICE Logs"
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 124,
        "question": "What are the benefits of storing the majority of an Application's server-side script logic in a Script Include?",
        "statement_options": {
            "a": "This makes execution faster.",
            "b": "Only run when called from a script.",
            "c": "The script logic can be hidden when the Application is installed from the ServiceNow Store.",
            "d": "For some changes to application logic there is only one place to make edits."
        },
        "selection_options": {
            "A": "a, b, and d",
            "B": "a, b, c, and d",
            "C": "b, c, and d",
            "D": "a, b, and c"
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 125,
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a Flow Designer feature?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Run a flow from a Catalog item",
            "B": "Call a flow from another flow or subflow",
            "C": "Add stages to a flow",
            "D": "Test a flow using the 'Run as' feature"
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 126,
        "question": "What is the purpose of the coalesce field when importing data?",
        "options": {
            "A": "If a match is not found, the existing record is updated",
            "B": "To determine if a record matches an existing record or is a new record",
            "C": "To identify and merge duplicate records",
            "D": "When a match is found, a new record is inserted"
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 127,
        "question": "If you create a SOAP Message what syntax indicates a variable to pass when the function is called?",
        "options": {
            "A": "current.variable_name",
            "B": "${variable_name}",
            "C": "variable_name.do?WSDL",
            "D": "< variable_name >"
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 128,
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a way to install an application on a ServiceNow instance?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Install an application from the Application Repository",
            "B": "Select the Copy button on the application record",
            "C": "Download and install an application from the ServiceNow Share web site",
            "D": "Download and install a third-party application from the ServiceNow Store"
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 129,
        "question": "Using Custom UI test step in Automated Test Framework, which of the following is NOT a testable page component?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Buttons",
            "B": "UI controls",
            "C": "UI pages",
            "D": "Form field values"
        },
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 130,
        "question": "Why create Applications in ServiceNow?",
        "statement_options": {
            "a": "To replace outdated, inadequate, custom business applications and processes",
            "b": "To extend service delivery and management to all enterprise departments",
            "c": "To allow users full access to all ServiceNow tables, records, and fields",
            "d": "To extend the value of ServiceNow"
        },
        "selection_options": {
            "A": "a, b, and d",
            "B": "a, b, c, and d",
            "C": "a, b, and c",
            "D": "b, c, and d"
        },
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 131,
        "question": "Flow Designer supports variable data types to store record data and complex data. Which of the following are supported variable data types? (Choose three.)",
        "options": {
            "A": "Choice data type",
            "B": "Array.Reference data type",
            "C": "Integer data type",
            "D": "Freedom data type",
            "E": "Array.Boolean data type",
            "F": "Label data type"
        },
        "answer": "ACE"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 132,
        "question": "Which of the following statements is true about Guided Application Creator?",
        "options": {
            "A": "The global scope option is turned on by default",
            "B": "Default access controls are automatically created",
            "C": "The welcome screen appears every time a new application is created",
            "D": "A scoped application user role is automatically created"
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 133,
        "question": "What are the ways to designate data tables when using Guided Application Creator (GAC)? (Choose three.)",
        "options": {
            "A": "Upload an existing PDF",
            "B": "Create a new table on the platform",
            "C": "Use a freeform database",
            "D": "Upload an existing spreadsheet",
            "E": "Use an existing table on the platform",
            "F": "Upload an existing word processing document"
        },
        "answer": "BDE"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 134,
        "question": "What is the Event Registry?",
        "options": {
            "A": "A Workflow which is launched every time an Event is generated; used to debug Events",
            "B": "The Event Log which lists all Events that have been generated",
            "C": "The method used in server side scripts to generate Events and pass parameters",
            "D": "A table containing a record for every Event known to the ServiceNow system which allows ServiceNow to react when Events are generated"
        },
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 135,
        "question": "Identify the ways an application can respond to an Event generated by the gs.eventQueue() method: (Choose two.)",
        "options": {
            "A": "Client Script",
            "B": "Email Notification",
            "C": "Scheduled Script Execution (Scheduled Job)",
            "D": "Script Action",
            "E": "UI Policy"
        },
        "answer": "BD"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 136,
        "question": "Is it possible to change an application's scope?",
        "options": {
            "A": "No, it's not possible",
            "B": "Yes, it's possible",
            "C": "Yes, but only from global scope to private scope",
            "D": "Yes, but only from private scope to global scope"
        },
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 137,
        "question": "Which of the following is true about g_scratchpad? (Choose two.)",
        "options": {
            "A": "Used to push information from the server to the client",
            "B": "Does not exist on the mobile platform",
            "C": "Has constructors and methods",
            "D": "Has default properties passed by client-side scripts"
        },
        "answer": "AB"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 138,
        "question": "Client-side scripts manage what?",
        "options": {
            "A": "User access",
            "B": "Database and backend",
            "C": "Playbook access",
            "D": "Forms and Form Fields"
        },
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 139,
        "question": "When debugging Email Notifications, what must you check on a user record? (Choose two.)",
        "options": {
            "A": "Active must be true.",
            "B": "The Email field must have a valid value.",
            "C": "The user must not be locked out.",
            "D": "The First name and Last name fields must have values.",
            "E": "Delegation must be enabled."
        },
        "answer": "AB"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 140,
        "question": "When crafting a scoped application that contains flow actions, what is the application called?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Action",
            "B": "Spoke",
            "C": "Bundle",
            "D": "Flow"
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 141,
        "question": "Which are reasons an application could be developed on the ServiceNow platform? (Choose three.)",
        "options": {
            "A": "It needs workflow to manage processes.",
            "B": "It requires reporting capabilities.",
            "C": "It uses forms extensively to interact with data.",
            "D": "It requires low-level programming libraries.",
            "E": "It uses multimedia features."
        },
        "answer": "ABC"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 142,
        "question": "Once an application is ready to share, which of the following methods of publishing are supported by ServiceNow? (Choose three.)",
        "options": {
            "A": "Publish to an application repository",
            "B": "Publish to a local drive",
            "C": "Publish to the ServiceNow Store",
            "D": "Publish to an Update Set",
            "E": "Publish to a spreadsheet",
            "F": "Publish to a local USB device"
        },
        "answer": "ACD"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 143,
        "question": "What is required to link a ServiceNow application to a Git repository? (Choose three.)",
        "options": {
            "A": "URI",
            "B": "ACL",
            "C": "Application name",
            "D": "Password",
            "E": "User name",
            "F": "URL"
        },
        "answer": "DEF"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 144,
        "question": "What is the Endpoint when configuring a REST Message?",
        "options": {
            "A": "The URI of the WebServer",
            "B": "The command to the REST script to stop execution",
            "C": "The URI of the data to be accessed, queried, or modified",
            "D": "The provider response indicates there is no data to send back"
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 145,
        "question": "Which client-side scripts apply to Record Producers? (Choose two.)",
        "options": {
            "A": "Fix Scripts",
            "B": "Catalog Client Scripts",
            "C": "UI Scripts",
            "D": "Catalog UI Policies",
            "E": "Record Producer Polices"
        },
        "answer": "BD"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 146,
        "question": "Which business requirements and process(es) should be documented as part of the application development plan? (Choose four.)",
        "options": {
            "A": "Available licenses",
            "B": "Business problem",
            "C": "Process steps",
            "D": "Users/stakeholders",
            "E": "Database capacity",
            "F": "Project schedule",
            "G": "Data input/output"
        },
        "answer": "BCDG"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 147,
        "question": "Which objects are used as part of the client-side scripting API? (Choose two.)",
        "options": {
            "A": "gs",
            "B": "current and previous",
            "C": "g_user",
            "D": "workflow.scratchpad",
            "E": "g_form"
        },
        "answer": "CE"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 148,
        "question": "When creating application tables, a user role is automatically added to the table record. Which other role does an application typically have?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Application Super User",
            "B": "Application Fulfiller",
            "C": "Application Admin",
            "D": "Application Manager"
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 149,
        "question": "Which determines the relationships between field in an Import Set table to field in an existing ServiceNow table?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Data Sources",
            "B": "Schema Map Relationship Builder",
            "C": "Business Service Management Map",
            "D": "Transform Map"
        },
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 150,
        "question": "What data types of Flow Designer variables are supported to store record data and complex data? (Choose three.)",
        "options": {
            "A": "Label data type",
            "B": "Integer",
            "C": "Array.Reference",
            "D": "Choice",
            "E": "String"
        },
        "answer": "BDE"
    }
]